Guide to the Jobs With Justice Records 2001-2012
Jobs With Justice Records
- B5: Regional Press Clippings; Misc. Print Materials; JWJ Early Years 1987 - (Box 8)
  - Jobs with Justice, Video, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Campaign for New Priorities, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Campaign for New Priorities, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Campaign for Workers Rights, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Jobs with Justice Press Clips, 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Transition Guide for Press Organizer, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Pamphlets, Programs and Mailings, 1997-2005 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- B6: JwJ Early Years cont.; Staff Materials 1999-2003; Retreats and Planning (Box 9)
  - Campaign for New Priorities, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - New Priorities Campaign, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Corporate Greed Day of Action Flyers, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - New Priorities Campaign, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fall Mobilization Against George Bush I, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - National Labor Rights Board Action News Clips, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    May 27 1993
  - Jobs with Justice Partnership for Democracy, Fiscal Sponsor, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Welfare, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    December 1997
  - Welfare Day of Action Press Clips, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Staff Report, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - General Electric Press Clips, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Jobs with Justice Welfare Publications, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Reform, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Anti-Contract on America, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    June 1995
  - Living Wage Packet and General Information, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Documents, 1993-1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Austin Cable Vision, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - AT&T Mobilization, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Planning Committee, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    June 24 2001
  - J4J DC and National, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Press Clips, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Field team, Anti Racism and Oppression, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    December 3 2005
  - Recent Staff Meeting, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Staff Meeting, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    March 5 2003
  - Field Team Retreats, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Personnel Policy, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Jobs with Justice Field Team, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Staff Meeting, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    April 9 2003
  - Staff Meeting, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    May 7 2003
  - Jobs with Justice Planning Committee and SGI Documents, Field Team, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    December 2000
  - Jobs with Justice Personnel Policy, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Jobs with Justice Staff Retreat, Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    May 9 2001
  - Criteria for Selecting Campaigns, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Staff Retreat, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    July 2003
  - 501c3 Application, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Jobs with Justice 501c3 Proof, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Strategic Planning Process Materials, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Jobs with Justice Affiliation and Chartering, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - AFSCME Fiscal Crisis, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Grinch Stuff, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Jobs with Justice Staff Meeting, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Jobs with Justice Board Meeting, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    May 10 and 11 2002
  - Board, Planning Committee, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Board, Planning Committee (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    October 6 and 7 2002
  - Staff Retreat, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Board, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Planning Committee Notes, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    contains floppy disc
- C1: Chartering Process 2003; Annual Meetings 1991-2001 (Box 10)
  - Jobs with Justice Charter Process, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Charter Memos, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    June 9 2003
  - Charter Process, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Charter Applications, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - North Texas, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Nova, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Portland, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Rochester, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - San Antonio, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Southeast Michigan, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - South Florida, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - St. Joseph Valley Project, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Western Massachusetts, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Rhode Island, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - St. Louis, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Toledo, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Triangle Area, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Tucson, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Utah, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Vermont, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - DC Jobs with Justice, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Columbus, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Colorado, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Eastern Massachusetts, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - ESSN, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Chicago, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Cleveland, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Long Island Charter, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Long Island, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Mahoning Valley, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Knoxville (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Kentucky, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Mid-Hudson Valley, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - New Mexico, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Atlanta, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Mid-Willamette Valley, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Milwaukee, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Montana, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Nashville, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - New York City, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Washington State Jobs with Justice, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Albany Jobs with Justice, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Albany Charter, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Austin, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Bloomington, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Buffalo, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Central Indiana Jobs with Justice, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Central Oregon Charter, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Eugene, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Annual Meeting Denver Expenses, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    March 1991
  - Annual Meeting Denver Handouts, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Annual Meeting Denver, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Annual Meeting Austin Expenses, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    February 1992
  - Annual Meeting Austin, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Annual Meeting Pittsburgh, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Annual Meeting Pittsburgh, Rooming Lists, Expenses, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Annual Meeting, Pittsburgh, Handouts, Slideshow, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Annual Meeting, Atlanta Handouts, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Annual Meeting, Atlanta, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Annual Meeting, Cleveland, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Planning Committee, Seattle Meeting, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Workshops, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Conference Evaluation, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - HUB, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Logistics, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Religion Labor Pre-Conference, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Seattle Annual Meeting, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    June 1996
  - Seattle Annual Meeting, Room and Catering Services, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Annual Meeting Seattle, Washington, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Jobs with Justice Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Workshops, Chicago Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Annual Meeting Registration, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Agenda, Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Meeting Rooms AV, etc. Chicago Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Ramada Alpha Lists, Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Chicago Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Chicago Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Annual Meeting Ad Book, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Speaker Talking Points, Annual meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Annual Meeting Agendas, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Religion and Labor Pre-Conference, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Interfaith Service Excerpts Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Annual Meeting Money, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Annual Meeting Recruitment, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Religion Labor Pre-Conference, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    Hebrew and English
  - Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Pre-Registration Mailing, Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    February 9 1999
  - Annual Meeting Schedule, 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Speaker Invites, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Conference Follow-Up, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Annual Meetings, Years Past, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 94)
- C2: Annual Meetings 2001-2005 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Labor Documents, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Map of Hotel and Convention Center, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - America's Center Agreement, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - America Center, Emails, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Annual Meeting, 1999-2005 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Millennium, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Meals, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - AV Needs, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Volunteer GRID (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting Brochure, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Entertainment, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Renaissance Hotel (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - SLAP, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Jobs with Justice Compiled Room List, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Pre-Conferences, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Clergy Session, Faith in Action, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Annual Meeting Lists, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Immigrant Rights Pre-Conference, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Strategy Sessions, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - General Sessions, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Annual Meeting Budget, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Dartmouth Jobs with Justice, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Annual Meeting Flyer, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Pride@Work Preconference, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Labor Organizations, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Recruitment Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Annual Meeting 2000 Recruitment (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Annual Meeting 2001 Report (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Annual meeting, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    September 6 - 9 2001. Cleveland, Ohio
  - Annual Meeting Program, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Workers' Rights Board, Annual Meeting Hearing, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Annual Meeting Ideas, Comments, etc., 2001 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Annual Meeting 2001 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Annual Meeting Debrief, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Annual Meeting Recruitment, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Annual Meeting Program, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Annual Meeting Flyer, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Annual Meeting Report, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Annual Meeting Thanks, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Jobs with Justice Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Wyndham Resorts, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Conference Agenda, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Annual Meeting Debrief, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Friday Night Banquet, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Annual Meeting Preparation, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Annual Meeting Thanks, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Annual Meeting Recruitment, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Annual Meeting Brochures, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Workshops, Annual Meeting 2003 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Jobs with Justice Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Jobs with Justice Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Program, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Recruitment, Organization Relations, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Annual Meeting Pre-Conferences, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Annual Meeting Program Committee, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Registration Packet, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Individual Donor list, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Retreats and Debrief, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Annual Meeting Information, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- C3: Annual Meetings 2005 cont.; Days of Action 1994-1998 (Box 12)
  - Annual Meeting Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting Hotel Reservations, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Facilities Documents, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Annotated Agenda, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Logistics, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Facilities, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - AV, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Childcare, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Translator and Documentation, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - National Day of Action, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Field Organizers, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Day of Action, Resources, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Media Relations Kit, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Public Jobs Creation, Meeting with Center for Community Change, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Day of Action Organization Kit, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    December 10 1997
  - Welfare Day of Action, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - National Day of Action for Welfare/Workfare Justice, Media Kit, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - National Day of Action for Welfare/Workfare Justice, Media Kit, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - National Day of Action for Welfare/Workfare Justice, Media Kit, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Day of Action Media, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Welfare Reform Documents, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Day of Action, Resource Materials III, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Religion DoA Packet, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Welfare Day of Action, Personal Stories, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Outreach, Day of Action, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Labor Pamphlets, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - General Day of Action Media, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Press Clips, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    December 1995
  - Press Clips Round 2, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Bellingham, Washington, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - "An Alternative Tashlich", 1997 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Richmond, Virginia, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Salt Lake City, Utah, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Seattle, Washington, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Charleston, West Virginia, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Coordinating Committee Weekly Updates, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Nationals to Locals, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Eugene, Oregon, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Columbia, South Carolina, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Charleston, South Carolina, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Knoxville, Tennessee, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Nashville, Tennessee, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - San Antonio, Texas, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Dallas, Texas, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Austin, Texas, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Louisville, Kentucky, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Augusta, Maine, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Salem, Massachusetts, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Framingham, Massachusetts, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Northampton, Massachusetts, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Boston, Massachusetts, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Providence, Rhode Island, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Rhode Island, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Baltimore, Maryland, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Detroit, Michigan, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Duluth, Minnesota, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - St. Louis, Missouri, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Jackson, Mississippi, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Missoula, Montana, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - New York, New York, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Patterson, New Jersey, 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Albany, New York, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Buffalo, New York, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Raleigh, Durham, North Carolina, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Lincoln, Nebraska, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Atlanta, Georgia, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Des Moines, Iowa, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Honolulu, Hawaii, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Boise, Idaho, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Chicago, Illinois, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Lakeland, Florida, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Bloomington, Indiana, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Indianapolis, Indiana, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Tallahassee, Florida, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Denver, Colorado, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - San Diego, California, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Los Angeles, California, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Oakland, San Francisco, California, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Jobs with Justice, Arkansas, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Phoenix, Arizona (Box 12, Folder 87)
- C4: Strike Support Late 1990s (Box 13)
  - Clinton Health Plan Lobby Kits, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Jobs with Justice Health Care Action Day Coordinators, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - CHA Organizations Use Our Materials, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Pre GGD Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - National Day of Action Against Corporate Greed, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    September 1996
  - June Day of Action and January - June Files, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - GE Contract Fight, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - US West Strike, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Gannett Action Organizing Materials, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    September 12 1997
  - Jobs with Justice and Teamsters UPS Strike, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - America West Appeal, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Ruiz Foods Script, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Teamster Appeal for Jobs with Justice Signatures, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Overnite, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Overnite, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Overnite, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Unions 101, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Week of Action 2009 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Jobs with Justice Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Annual Meeting Agenda Documents, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Jobs with Justice Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - NEA Expo, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Speakers, Workshop Invites Contact Information, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Cleveland Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Mailings, Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Miami Numbers and Hotel Information, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Contacts, Planning Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Music and Art, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Annual Meeting 2003 Samples (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Campus Worker Manual, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    June 2001
  - SLAP Goals, 2003-2005 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- D1: Treston Davis Faulkner Files: Field Work and Campus Work (Box 14)
  - Field Action News, 1999-2006 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - USAS Materials, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - United Farm Workers, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    November 25 1997
  - Labor, NAFTA and APEC, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - SLAP, Day of Action, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - SLAP Day of Action, 2000-2008 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - UFW, Strawberry Campaign, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - GROW, Other Training, Living Wage, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - AT&T Comcast Merger, CWA, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Jobs Loss and Recession Post 9-11, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Health Care Field Work, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Smithfield Blank Sign in Sheets, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Field Action, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Field Notes and Materials, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    April 2002
  - April Press Clips, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - General Field Team, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Field Team General, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Field Team, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Media Tool Kit, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Funding, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Public Welfare Campaign Final Report, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Labor Publications, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Labor Documents, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - "World", 2001 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - "World", 2001 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - "World" and Miscellaneous Documents, 1999-2001 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Temple University and Public Education, 1992-1999 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Drug Policy in Schools, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Documents, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Jobs with Justice Planning Stuff, SLAP, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - SLAP Presentation Strategy, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Campaigns, SLAP Related, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Jobs with Justice and SLAP Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Jobs with Justice Transition Materials, SLAP, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - USSA Transition Materials, SLAP, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Memos and Emails, SLAP, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- D2: Treston Davis Faulkner Files: Field Work and Campus Work (Box 15)
  - Rebuilding Bridges, The New Connection Between Students and Labor, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    November 12 - 14 1999. Cornell University
  - General Living Wage Information, 2000-2006 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Living Wage Resources, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Talking Points (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Manual Stuff (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sample press Releases, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - SLAP Press April 4 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Job Application, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Evaluations, 2005-2006 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - January 20-22 Evaluations, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - GROW Strategy Chart, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Direct Action Handouts (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Group Dynamics, Consensus (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Group Dynamics Questions (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Campus Living Wage Project, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - UC San Diego Demands (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - UC San Diego (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Georgetown University Demands (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Georgetown Articles, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Georgetown Policy, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Washington University Survey (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Washington University Case Study, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Harvard and Campus Living Wage, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Spring and Summer 2001
  - Harvard Living Wage, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - April 4 2002 Materials (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - April 4 2002 Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - April 4 2002 Outreach and Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - SLAP Material Requests, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - April 4 2001 Materials (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - April 4 2001 Grid and Numbers (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - April 4 2001 Planning (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - April 4 2001 Organizing Kit (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - A4 2001 Media and Flyers, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - April 4 2000 Materials (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - April 4 2000 Day of Action Media Stuff, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - April 4 Local Reports, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - April 2000 Materials (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Jobs with Justice USSA Materials, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Highlights April 4 2000 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Day of Action Media Kit, Organizing Kit and Grid, D10 1997 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - USSA Strategic Planning, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - USSA Manual, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - General Materials (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - General Workshop Evaluation, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Highlander Training, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - United Council's Building Unity Conference (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - United Council's Annual Building Unity Conference, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    November 16 - 18 2001
  - Student-Labor Roundtable Agenda and Sign-In Sheet, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    October 24 2001
  - Miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- D3: Treston Davis Faulkner Files: Field Work and Campus Work (Box 16)
  - Political Activism Documents, 1999-2003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - USSA Legislative Conference 2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - USSA Board of Directors Meeting, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    San Diego, California. January 2001.